Gershenfeld, Walter and Gladys Arbitration Papers 6344
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Walter and Gladys Gershenfeld Arbitration Papers
1932-2010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Gershenfeld, Walter J.
Gershenfeld, Gladys
Waltcher, Gladys
Cutcher-Gershenfeld, Joel
National Academy of Arbitrators (NAA)
American Arbitration Association (AAA)
6344
12 cubic feet
12 linear ft.
Collective labor agreements.
7756475
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 19, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 26, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Arbitration, Industrial; Collective bargaining; Gernshenfeld, Walter J.; Gershenfeld, Gladys; Waltcher, Gladys; Cutcher-Gershenfeld, Joel; American Arbitration Association (AAA); Industrial Relations and Research Association (IRRA); Labor and Employment Relations Association (LERA); National Academy of Arbitrators (NAA)
7756475
- AAA, NAA, IRRA/LERA Files (Box 1)
  - AAA Training, 1996-2002 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AAA Taskforce, 1976-2003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - DALC, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - AAA Training, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Hospital Organizing Drive 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Art Mehr Party 3/88, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - AAA Cases, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - AAA Advisory, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - AAA Arb. Ting w/ NAA, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - AAA, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - AAA, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - AAA, Baltimore 5/4/88, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration General, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration - Training, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - AAA, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - AAA, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Commercial Arbitration, 1994-1999 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Disconnects, 1985-2003 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - DALC, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - NAA Committees, General, 2002-2004 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - NAA Las Vegas Program, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Sister + Interest Camden, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Projects + Proposals, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - NAA - CPRG, 1999-2003 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - NAA - OPC, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - FTC (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Academy - General, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Alliance, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - NAA - BOG, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Col. Barg., 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - SEPTA (0458) - Hanis 8/01, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Ethics Training, 1988-2008 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Managing the Hearing NAA/98, 1989-1998 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Writing Seminar NAA 2003 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - NAA (Admission), 1969-1981 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - AAA Article, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - NAA General, 2000-2002 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Scope and Contents
    1 photograph
  - NAA, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - NAA Chronicle, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Arbitration Booklet, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - NAA Insurance, 2001-2007 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - NAA, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Agenda, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Subcontracting, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - NAA, 1998-2003 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - NAA, 1986-2003 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Nat Acad of Arbitrators, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - NAA Mailist, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - NAA, 2004-2009 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Vcs. Aqv. Liais. Comm., 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - NAA History Committee Interview 1994 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - EEOC (Maslanich) 12/98, 1993-2001 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Common Law, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - NAA - Region, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - NAA 2004 Fall Education Conference (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - NAA - Future, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Opening Statements NAA 5/02, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Emp. Arb., 2005 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - LERA, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - IRRA/LERA, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - OPC, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Social Contract, 1995-2007 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - I.R.R.A., 1955-2001 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - I.R.R.A. 1980 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - I.R.R.A., 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - I.R.R.A. - Detroit - April 1985 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence, 1973-1993 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - University of Groningen, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Groningen, 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Bemis Bag Settled 4/87, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Misc., 1998 (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Cornell, Philadelphian Owner's Internal Disputes Resolution Committee, Subject files (Box 2)
  - Arbitration, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - FMCS General, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Focus Grp., 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - SPIDR Conferences PHL 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Alliances, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - FMCS, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - FMCS, 1970-1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - FMCS Training, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - FMCS Arb. Mtg. PCTS. C, 1982-1987 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - FMCS Symposium 2003+2004 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Neutrals Extra (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Cornell University (General) WSB, 1950-1953 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Cornell Arrangements Oct. 2006, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Walt Cornell, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Arrangements, 2004-2007 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Alliance Nov. 2000 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Research Articles, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - EECC, 2000-2004 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Competce Club, 2002-2005 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Abuams, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - IDRC, 2001-2007 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - IDRC, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - IDRC, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - DOL, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - IDRC Complaint Forms, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Hernick - Deutsch, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Lempirt - Finston, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Cole - Santaro, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - DelMaestro - Gigliott, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Bebe Weiss, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Mebbit - IBT OT, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Walter Gershenfeld Biographical, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - NMB, 1991-2002 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - UWI, 1974-1978 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - DOD, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Letters that Matter, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - CCCC, 2005-2010 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Cervont. Corresp., 2001-2009 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Corresp., 2003-2007 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Corresp., 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Gladys ands Walter Gershenfeld, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence, 2001-2006 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Arbitration + MSPB FSLRP - 5/85, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Delinquents, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Apparel + Textile Ind., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Collective Bargaining Case Study Remple Teach. Conf. 1980 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - State Librarians - Sept 1979 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - McGill Conference 3/82, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Numbers Game, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - U.S. Col. Barg. System (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Arbitration Practice (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Health Conference 5/85, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Fels Class (Ferman) Sp. 88, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Gershenfeld Relatives, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Geo. Taylor Award, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - SS- Talks, 1982-2007 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Publication of Awards, 1974-1980 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Collective Bargaining, 1986-2006 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Gaylestown Borough + Police Association settled 6/88, 1988-2008 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Gov. Govt., 2007 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Misc., 1993-2007 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Misc., 1981 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Civil Defense (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - ACLU - Civil Liberties, 1956-1962 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Mediator Papers, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Special Magistrate W.J.G., 2005-2007 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Arthur Marsh Visit, 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Walter Gershenfeld Interview, 2003-2005 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Subject files (Box 3)
  - PA Labor Law, 2000-2002 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Fl Perc, 1999-2002 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - PLRB - Training Sessions May - June 1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - PLRB Fact Finding Aug 92, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - PLRB, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - PLRB - Pa. Laws, 1949-1976 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Teaching Conf., 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Prof. Workers Monograph, 1974-1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Prof., 1982-1989 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - LAA + Individual Cases, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Gladys Program 87, 1995-1997 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Gladys Programs, 1982-1988 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Gladys Program, 1980-1987 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Gladys Programs, 1978-1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Gladys Program, 1969-1995 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Ed Beal - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Genose Issues, 1985-1996 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Ed Beal, 1976-1984 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Edwin Bael Personnel Management, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Edwin Bael Personnel Management Draft Chapters 4-7 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Doctor Research Project Gladys Gershenfeld, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Writing - G.G., 1985-2003 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Personnel Notes + Special Requests, 1978-1986 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Subpoenas, 1978-2000 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Writing - Other Authors, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Gladys - Employment Women, 1980-2006 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    6 Photographs
  - Employment, 1978-2006 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - The Right to Keep and Bear Arms, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Absenteeism, 1973-1990 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Gershenfeld, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Janice Booker Across from the Alley Next Door to the Door to the Roolroom (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Current Articles, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Conduct of the Hearing 9-16 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Articles, 2004-2007 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - emails, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Or Wadash - Study Group, 2002-2006 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Zionism, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - EEOC, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - FL Management Services, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - GG Arbitration Income, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Good Shepard Mediation Center 1987-1998 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Philadelphia College of Textile and Science, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Subject files (Box 4)
  - Upcoming Events, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - AJC-ECUMCNICAC, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Public Sector, 2000-2003 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - PCTA Employment, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Joel, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Gladys. Early Employment, 1953-1969 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Gladys - Personal, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - BU Five, 2006-2008 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Walter Gershenfeld Personal 1955-1965 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Walter Gershenfeld Personal 1965-1969 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Walter Gershenfeld, Personal 1970-, 1972-1976 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Condolences, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Miscellany, 1992-1995 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    1 Photograph
  - Insurance, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - California Western Univ. Admission - Official Data, 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Thesis Proposal, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Doctoral Research Project, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Class Notes (Source Materials), 1955-1973 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - California Western Alumni Assn., 1982 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Resumes (Family), 1983 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Doctoral Research Project Gladys Gershenfeld, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Photographs (Box 4, Folder 22)
    13 Photographs
  - Absenteeism - Framalo, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Papers (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - CCH Cases, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Mainting Practice, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Speeches, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Academy - Exec. Cutter., 1990-2011 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Absenteeism, Cases, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Assertation Date, 1980-1984 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - The Lore of the Shop (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Finished Copy (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Neo-conservatism (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Cr Modest, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous, 1998-2008 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Gladys Gershenfeld Arbitration Files, 1972-2004 (Box 5)
  - GiG Arbitration Summary, 1982-2000 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Selected Cases 1972-1978 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Selected Cases 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Pan Am Navy Yard 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration Cases Iam.-Apr. 1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Arbitration Cases May-Dec. 1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Arbitration Awards Jan. 91 - May 91, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Arbitration Awards June - Dec. 1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Arbitration Cases Jan. Aug. 92, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Arb. Awards Dec. 92 - Mar. 93, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Arb. Awards Apr. - July 1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Arbitration Awards Sept. 93 - Mar. 94, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - ILR Founders Seminar 1975, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration Awards 1995 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Arb. Awards 1996 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - RR - PEB Appointment 8/96, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Arb. Awards 12-97 - 11-98, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Arbitration Cases Jan. - June 99, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Connection, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Arb. Awards 2001 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Health + Human Service, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Arbitration Awards 2002 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Arbitration Awards 2003, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Post Authority Allegheny County, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - EEOC. Med. Contract 2001 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Arbitration Awards 2004 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Gladys Gershenfeld Arbitration Files, 2004-2008 (Box 6)
  - New Jersey PERC, 1994-2004 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - H + HS Exhibits, 1995-1998 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Giant Foods, Inc., 2004 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Fl Mgt. Dept., 2004 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Arbitration Awards 2005 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Economic Development Adm. June 05, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - ACME - Teamsters 771 Cancelled 5/05, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Delcore - 115 7/05, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - ARMY, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - HRSA 2 2/05, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Health Resources + Services, 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Septa + TWUA 4199, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Department of Commerce, Economic Development Administration and American Federation of Government Employees, AFL-CIO Local 3810, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration Grievant's Exhibits File Gladys Gershenfeld - Arbitratior (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Memorandums and Notifications Folder 1, 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Memorandum's and Notifications Folder 2, 2001-2004 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Memorandum's and Notifications Folder 3, 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - PA Chemical Schools, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Com of Pa. PSSU, 2002-2006 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - York County Nursing Home 8/06, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - AirTran 041204, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Borough of Pottstown, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - County of Northampton 01979, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Cocoa + PBA, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - NASD 05-6048 (settled), 2006 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - NASD 06-3307 (Olson), 2007 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - FINRA #07-0415 Smell, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - DOD-FEA, 2005-2007 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Spruce Manor, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - NASD 065389 (T.Walter) (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - County of Westchester Jan 07, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Disputes 2007 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Mutual Service Corporation (Folder 1 of 3) 2008 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Mutual Service Corporation (Folder 3 of 3), 2005 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Mutual Service Corporation (Folder 2 of 3), 2008 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Gladys Gershenfeld Arbitration Files, 2009; Walter Gershenfeld Arbitration Files, 1967-1982 (Box 7)
  - 1982 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 1981 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 1979 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 1977 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 1976 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 1975 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Phota - School Dist.- Phila. Fed of Tchrs., 1974 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Frnak - Teamsters Local 312 Cancelled '74, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - ITE - IBEW (1176) '74, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Commonwealth of Pa. + Pa. Stats Police '73, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - PSSU - U.S. Commonwealth Stewards '74, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Delaval - USW '74, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Local 312 IBT Matlock '74, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - TRW - Highway Truck Drivers Local 107, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Local 8-898 OCAW Getty Oil FMCS '74, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Pvct. Mct. Serv. Co. United Ind. Un. '74, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Amstar - Local 56 Amal. Food. '74, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - United Steelworkers - Staffmans Org. Comm. '74, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - American Ca, Local 712 Int'l. Print. Pressmen '74, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Common. Us. AFSME Padula '74, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Roberts Packing Co. - Local 195, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - 1974 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - School Dist. Of Phila.- P.F.T. (summer School), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - City of Lebanon - FOP -'73, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Oxford School District/ PSEA, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - PFT - Sch. Dist. Of Phila. (coaches), 1973 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Music IAM, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - PFT - Sch. Dist. Of Phila. - Liebeuman - Swim, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Local 1952 - IAFF - Lebanon '73, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - 1973 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - 1972 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - 1971 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - 1970 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - 1969 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - 1968 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - 1967 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - FINRA #08-00748, 2008-2010 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - NASD 05-2007 (Ianco) (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Florida PERC Act + Rules, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Walter Gershenfeld Arbitration Files, 1983-1995 (Box 8)
  - 1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - ACME Markets -and- Local 72, UFCW 1983 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Bensalem S.I. Local 1201. Firemen, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Bishop McCarthy Residence -and- Local 56, UFCW, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - York County Bridge -and- Teamstars Local 430, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Lenap o Forgo -and- Local 7207, USW, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Tri-state-Local 107 ILGWU, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Hahnemann University, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - P. Dist. 81, Local 1915, AFSCME -and- Dep't. of Public. Safety Del.), 1983 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - 1984 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - RCA -and- IUE, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Lenape Forge -and- U.S.W., 1984 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - FOP, Lodge 112 -and- City of Harrisburg, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - 1985 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - 1986 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - 1987 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - 1988 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - 1989 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - 1990 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - 1991 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - 1992 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - 1993 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - 1994, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - 1995 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Walter Gershenfeld Arbitration Files, 1996-2003 (Box 9)
  - 1996 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 1996 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - 1997 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - 1998 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - 1999 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - 2000 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - 2001 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - SEPTA - TRANSI POL, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Chester - Upland PSEA, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Kivz-115, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Smurfit - Pace, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Local 655 American Federation of Musicians, AFL-CIO -and- Florida Philharmonic Orchestra, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - ICT, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - 2001 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - 2002 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Collective Bargaining (Mining), 2002 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - ATPK - IBT, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Up. Marc. F+P, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Penske - IBT 390, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Bucks County + AFSCME, 2000-2003 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - TIAXE 2002 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - sub markets of Cherry Hill - UFCW 2002 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Council Rock - PSEA, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Remmey Wood Products Teamsters Local 470 1975 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Dupont Ampthill, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Bensalem EA SD, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Helmics - 115 IBT, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Penske - IBT, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Post - IBT 830, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Bristol SD + EA, 2000-2002 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Brune's UFCW, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - 2002, 1988-2002 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - 2003 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Supermarkets of Cherry Hill UFCW Van Drivers, 2002-2004 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Units stat. MD - IBT 570, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Hyatt Reg. - Here Local 274, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Craftex - UNITE, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - North Phila - H.S. 11990, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - US Pipe - USW, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Perf. Const. Sves. + Cement Masons, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Hannemann - 11991, 1999-2003 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Geissinger - D1199 C, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Walter Gershenfeld Arbitration Files, 2004-2008, Calendars and Account Books (Box 10)
  - 2004 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Rose Tree Media + School District, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Edwards, Edwin Temple University Hospital, 2000-2004 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Special Master, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Daytona Beach - AFSCME, 2002-2004 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Elaryn - PSSO Hidges, 2001-2004 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Muhlendberg - IBT, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Fairmint Products + IBT 764, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Temple Hosp. - 11996 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Tropicarn - Here (54), 2004 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Radnor SD + EA, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Wissahickson SD - PSEA, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Corp. and USWA CWA - Verizon, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - 2005 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Pfizer - Abella, 2003-2005 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Pfizer - Watson, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Showboat Klitsch, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Natl. Publ. Co. GCIU, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - (Munford), 2005 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Sodexho - HERE, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Glou. Term - Dock Workers (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Nauticals Conf., 2005 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Costco IBT, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - CWA & Verizon 2005, 1992-2007 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Wood Company Puerto Rico, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - ACME - IBT 771, 2004-2005 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Arkema - USA, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Verizon, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Hahn 1199, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - 2006 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Mogul, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - IBT Showboat, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Southeast Delco SD + EA, 2004-2006 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - U.S. Pipe - USA, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Jersey Eagle Sales - IBT 125, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Waste Mgt. IBT 115, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Mcubed - IBT, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - 2007 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Phila. - Police, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Atto - Gen. FOP, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Harran's - HERE, 2005-2007 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Phl. - Police Nosik, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Borgata, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Zallies, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Robert Bigelow -can- Terminal, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Kissconon IAFF, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - CSTX - IAM, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Cloucester Terms Dock Wkrs., 2007 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Manahan - SunGard Collegis, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Schuylkill AFSCME, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Phila. AFSCME, 2005-2006 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - 2008, 2007-2008 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Kellogg - BCTGM, 2005-2008 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Planners and Booklets, 1998-2006 (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Publications, 1943-1983 (Box 11)
  - 1981 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 1980 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 1979 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 1978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 1976 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 1976 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 1975 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 1973 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 1972 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 1971 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 1970 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - 1969 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - July - Oct 1968 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Jan-June 1968 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - 1967 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - 1966 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - 1965 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - 1964 (Box 11, Folder 18)